Guide to the Ira Silverberg Papers MSS.110
Fales Library and Special Collections
Ira Silverberg Papers
1980-2015
Fales Library and Special Collections
Silverberg, Ira
MSS.110
70.8 Linear Feet in 53 record cartons, 29 manuscript boxes, 3 flat boxes, 41 boxes, and 16 flat file folders
Ira Silverberg has been an influential literary agent and editor in New York City for almost two decades. His papers contain the correspondence and manuscripts of many of the city's young talents. Additionally, his papers offer a unique insight into the world of New York City publishing. Of special interest in the Silverberg papers is the extensive amount of material relating to authors Kathy Acker, William S. Burroughs and Dennis Cooper.
Access Restrictions
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Biographical Note
Ira Silverberg has been influential in the Downtown scene in his capacity as both literary agent and editor. Silverberg has been a literary agent at Donadio & Ashworth, Editor-in-Chief at Grove/Atlantic Press, and editorial and publishing director at Serpent's Tail's U.S. projects, High Risk Books and Midnight Classics. He also developed the marketing and public relations firm, Ira Silverberg Communications, which as attracted such prestigious clients as: The Academy of American Poets, William S. Burroughs, Dennis Cooper, City Lights Publications, Re/Search Publications, and the estate of David Wojnarowicz.
Silverberg began his career in publishing in 1984 as an Editorial and Publicity Assistant at The Overlook Press. In 1985, he was named Publicity Director of Grove Press. He left Grove in 1990 to begin work for Serpent's Tail. He returned to Grove/Atlantic in 1997 before moving on to Donadio & Ashworth.
While working for Serpent's Tail, Silverberg co-edited two anthologies, High Risk (Dutton/Plume U.S.; Serpent's Tail U.K.) and High Risk 2 (Plume U.S.; Serpent's Tail U. K.), that proved influential in defining the Downtown aesthetic. Many of the then-unknown authors included went on to have successful and prolific careers.
In addition to his publishing and editorial duties Silverberg has become affiliated with many cultural institutions in New York City. He serves on the Board of Directors of BOMB magazine and the Member's Council of PEN American Center. He has also acted as judge for the Gregory Kolovakos Award for AIDS writing; he has been a panelist for the National Endowment for the Arts Literature Program and the Lila Wallace-Reader's Digest Fund; and he has acted as editorial advisor to the Portable Lower East Side. He has also served as a member of the visiting faculty at The New School for Social Research.
Scope and Content
The Ira Silverberg papers contain correspondence, manuscripts, subject files, business/administrative files, personal files, cassette tapes, videos, books, periodicals, posters, and three-dimensional objects. The following is a brief series description that provides a general guide to the contents of each series.
Series I: Correspondence - Includes correspondence to and from Ira Silverberg, with correspondents such as Kathy Acker, Lawrence Chua, Dennis Cooper, Tim Dlugos, Gary Indiana, James Purdy, Jon Savage, Art Spiegelman, Lynne Tillman, John Waters, and David Wojnarowicz, as well as correspondence regarding certain writers, namely Kathy Acker and Jacqueline Susann. This series is arranged alphabetically by correspondent.
Series II: Manuscripts - Includes manuscripts received by Ira Silverberg, such as those by Dennis Cooper, Lawrence Chua, Karen Finley, Allen Ginsberg, Lynne Tillman, David Trinidad, John Waters, and David Wojnarowicz. This series is arranged alphabetically by author.
Series III: Affiliations - Includes correspondence and related materials involving Ira Silverberg's affiliations, such as with the Academy of American Poets, CLMP, the New School, and PEN. This series is arranged alphabetically by institution.
Series IV: Business/Administration Files - Includes files relating to Ira Silverberg's various positions as editor and literary agent, such as activity reports, contracts, general business correspondence, events, insurance, tax files, mailing lists, and notebooks. This series also includes correspondence and related files regarding Silverberg's business associates and contacts, such as Donadio & Ashworth, Grove/Atlantic, Peake Associates, Re/Search Publishing, and Serpent's Tail/High Risk. The files in this series are arranged alphabetically by subject.
Subseries A: General Business/Administration Files
Subseries B: Client Projects - Includes files related to projects by Silverberg's clients, especially projects by Kathey Acker, Dennis Cooper, Richard Grossman and Gary Indiana. Files are arranged by client name when known, or by original folder title when client is unspecificed.
Subseries C: Financial Files - The majority of this subseries consists of receipts, bills, and other financial documentation. Arranged aplphabetically by original folder title, and then chronologically.
Subseries D: Tear Sheets, Reviews and Clippings - Various press clippings relating to Silverberg's projects and clients. Arranged alphabetically by client name or subject when known, or chronologically as general "tear sheets" files.
Series V: Personal Files - Includes articles by and about Ira Silverberg, Silverberg bios, Personal correspondence, personal finances, and photographs. The 2005 accretion includes a large number of photographs and negatives. This series is arranged alphabetically by subject.
Series VI: Computer Files - Includes information downloaded from Silverberg's hard drive and computer disks, as well as the actual disks themselves. Files include, Kathy Acker, client lists, bios, William S. Burroughs, and email correspondence. This series is arranged alphabetically by the file names given by Silverberg. The actual disks are listed at the end.
Series VII: Other Media - Includes cassette tapes, compact disks, DVDs, and movie film arranged alphabetically by title.
Series VIII: Books/Periodicals - Includes books and periodicals collected by Silverberg and arranged alphabetically by title. Books and periodicals not found in the New York University catalog (Bobcat) were catalogued and are now shelved in the Downtown Collection in the Fales Library and Special Collections.
Series IX: Burroughs - Includes materials relating to William S. Burroughs, such as a variety of Burroughs's projects, Burroughs-related manuscripts, correspondence between Burroughs, James Grauerholz, and Ira Silverberg, Burroughs-related events, and Burroughs photographs. This series is arranged alphabetically by subject, based on original file titles.
Series X: Ephemera - Includes one box containing Jacqueline Susann publicity from Grove/Atlantic, and one box of three-dimensional objects.
Series XI: J.T. LeRoy - The majority is clippings and correspondence. The clippings are largely reviews of LeRoy's books, or articles about the LeRoy "hoax." The correspondence consists of email printouts, faxes, and letters, mostly about LeRoy, although some of the correspondence is from "J.T. LeRoy" to Silverberg. Folders are arranged alphabetically by title, and materials within are arranged chronologically.
Map Case 1: Oversize - Currently unprocessed. Includes movie posters and original artwork.
Arrangement
Folders are arranged alphabetically by subject/author heading, and then chronologically.
The Ira Silverberg Papers are organized by subject into eleven series.
Missing Title
Group 1, Series I: Correspondence
Group 1, Series II: Manuscripts
Group 1, Series III: Affiliations
Group 1, Series IV: Business/Administrative Files
Group 1, Series V: Personal Files
Group 1, Series VI: Computer Files
Group 1, Series VII: Other Media
Group 1, Series VIII: Books/Periodicals
Group 1, Series IX: Burroughs
Group 1, Series X: Ephemera
Group 1, Series XI: J.T. Leroy
Group 2, Series I: Correspondence
Group 2, Series II: Manuscripts
Group 2, Series IV: Business/Administrative Files
Group 2, Series VIII: Books/Periodicals
Group 2, Series IX: Burroughs
Group 3, Series I: Correspondence
Group 3, Series II: Manuscripts
Group 3, Series III: Affiliations
Group 3, Series IV: Business/Administration Files
Group 3, Series V: Personal Files
Group 3, Series VI: Computer Files
Group 3, Series VII: Other Media
Group 3, Series VIII: Books/Periodicals
Group 3, Series IX: Burroughs
Group 3, Series X: Ephemera
Oversize I
2016 Accretion
Oversize II
Related Material at the Fales Library and Special Collections
Dennis Cooper Papers (MSS.085)
Tim Dlugos Papers (MSS.087)
Serpents Tail/High Risk Archive (MSS.086)
David Wojnarowicz Papers (MSS.092)
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Ira Silverberg Papers were donated to the Fales Library by Ira Silverberg 2001, with additional donations in 2003, 2005, 2007, 2008, 2009, 2010, and 2016. The accession numbers associated with this collection are 2001.110, 2003.110, 2005.110, 2007.110, 2008.110, 2009.110, 2010.110, and 2016.006.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Access to some audiovisual materials in this collection is available through digitized access copies. Researchers may view an item's original container, but the media themselves are not available for playback because of preservation concerns. Materials that have already been digitized are noted in the collection's finding aid and can be requested in our reading room. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact special.collections@nyu.edu with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Magnetic disks.; Magazines (Periodicals); Manuscripts for publication.; New York (N.Y.).; Books.; Authors and publishers.; Publishers and publishing in literature.; Literary movements -- United States.; New York (N.Y.) -- Intellectual life -- 20th century.; Audiotapes.; Literature, Experimental.; Videocassettes.; business records; Authors, American -- 20th century.; Dlugos, Tim; Waters, Jon; Tillman, Lynne; Susann, Jacqueline; Spiegelman, Art; Cooper, Dennis, 1953-; Acker, Kathy, 1948-1997; Indiana, Gary; High Risk Books (Firm); Burroughs, William S., 1914-1997; Purdy, James; Wojnarowicz, David
- Group 1, Series I: Correspondence
  - Acker, Kathy-Correspondence with Silverberg, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Acker, Kathy-Correspondence re: Acker, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Acker, Kathy-Correspondence re: Acker, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Acker, Kathy-Correspondence re: Acker, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Acker, Kathy-Correspondence re: Acker printed from Silverberg's computer, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Acker, Kathy-Obituaries / Commemorations, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Acker, Kathy-Photographs, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - American Chameleon. Richard O. Curry and Lawrence B. Goodheart, editors, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - American Poetry: The Twentieth Century, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Antoni, Brian, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Apfelschnitt, Carl, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Armitage, Simon, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Bergen, Ronald, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Berzon, Betty, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Bibby, James, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Bockris, Victor, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Bonner, Hilary, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Brownstein, Michael, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Bruno, Guiliana, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Byng, Jaime, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Carr, C., undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Chua, Lawrence-Correspondence, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Chua, Lawrence-Contract with Grove/Atlantic, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Chua, Lawrence-Reviews of Gold By the Inch, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Chua, Lawrence-Proposals, Author Questionnaire, Miscellany, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Clews, Alan, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Cliff, Michelle, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Coe, Jonathan-The Dwarves of Death correspondence, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Coe, Jonathan-House of Sleep correspondence, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Coe, Jonathan-What a Carve Up!/The Winshaw Legacy correspondence and reviews, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Cohen, Lisa, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Cooper, Dennis-General Correspondence, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Cooper, Dennis-Closer, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Cooper, Dennis-Closer-William S. Burroughs notes re: Closer, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Cooper, Dennis-The Dream Police, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Cooper, Dennis-Frisk, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Cooper, Dennis-Guide, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Cooper, Dennis-Horror Hospital, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Cooper, Dennis-Jerk, undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Cooper, Dennis-Period, undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Cooper, Dennis- The Tenderness of the Wolves, undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Cooper, Dennis-Try, undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Cooper, Dennis-Wrong, undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Cooper, Dennis-Articles about Dennis Cooper, undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Cooper, Dennis-Articles by Dennis Cooper, undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Cooper, Dennis-Contracts, undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Cooper, Dennis-Correspondence from Dennis Cooper to Mark Pahl L'Ilith re: Antichrist Superstud by Mark Pahl L'Ilith and the publishing business, undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Cooper, Dennis-Interview, undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Cooper, Dennis-New York University, Fales Library-Contract/Correspondence, undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Cooper, Dennis-Project Proposals, undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Coover, Robert, undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Crasta, Richard, undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Crosbie, Lynn, undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - David, Lawrence, undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Dlugos, Tim, undated (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Doolittle, Jerome, undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Estep, Maggie, undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Ezersky, Lauren, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Field, Edward, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Finley, Karen, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Friedman, Seth, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Galgutt, Damon, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Gerald, Marc, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Gillison, Samantha, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Globert, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Graf, Pete, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Grossman, Richard, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Gysin, Brion, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Hadley, Leila, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Harding, James, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Harris, Rolf, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Hayes, Charles, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Hemphill, Essex, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Hirschhorn, Clive, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Hoskyns, Barney, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Indiana, Gary, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Jarman, Derek, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Jones, Dylan, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Kelly, Steven, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Kertess, Klaus, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Leffingwell, Ed, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Lucas, Christopher, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - MacAnna, Ferdia, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Manrique, Jaime, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Meer, Ameena, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Metalious, Grace, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Morrisroe, Mark, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Naher, Gaby, undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Newton, Fredrika, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Ohle, David, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Patterson, Gareth, undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Pelevin, Victor, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Pierson, Jack, undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Pessoa, Fernando, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Potter, Dennis, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Purdy, James, undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Reed, Jeremy, undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Reynolds, Simon, undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Rimmer, David, undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Romberger, James, undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Rouband, Jacques, undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Savage, Jon-General Correspondence, undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Savage, Jon-England's Dreaming, undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Savage, Jon-Teenage, undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Savage, Jon-Time Travel, undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Smith, Rupert, undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Snail, Azalia, undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Spiegelman, Art, undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Stadler, Matthew, undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Stevens, Jay, undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Stockly, Charles, undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Stone, Laurie, undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Susann, Jacqueline-General Correspondence re: Jacqueline Susann, undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Susann, Jacqueline-Publicity, Book Reviews, and Press Releases, undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Susann, Jacqueline-Publicity, Book Reviews, and Press Releases, undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Susann, Jacqueline-Event Flyers, undated (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Susann, Jacqueline-Correspondence re: Jacqueline Susann Panels, undated (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Susann, Jacqueline-Valley of the Dolls-Review (cassette tape), undated (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Susann, Jacqueline-Jacqueline Susann Archive, undated (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Susann, Jacqueline-Grove/Atlantic Contract, undated (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Susann, Jacqueline-Notes on Every Night Josephine!, undated (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Susann, Jacqueline-Book Covers, undated (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Susann, Jacqueline-Photographs/Slides, undated (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Susann, Jacqueline-Dead Jackie Susann Quarterly, issues 1 and 2, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Tillman, Lynne, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Timpanelli, Gioia, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Tlali, Miriam, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Trocchi, Alexander, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Ullman, Ellen, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Warhol, Andy, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Waters, John, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Wells, Steven, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - West, Paul, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - White, Tony, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Wojnarowicz, David-General Correspondence re: David Wojnarowicz, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Wojnarowicz, David-Close to the Knives, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Wojnarowicz, David-Close to the Knives, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Wojnarowicz, David-Memories that Smell Like Gasoline, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Wojnarowicz, David-Seven Miles a Second, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Wojnarowicz, David-Tongues of Flame, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Wojnarowicz, David-The Waterfront Journals, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Wojnarowicz, David-articles re: David Wojnarowicz, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Wojnarowicz, David-Royalties Paid to the Estate of David Wojnarowicz, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Wojnarowicz, David-Interview with Nan Goldin, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Wojnarowicz, David-Interview with Sylv Lotringer, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Wojnarowicz, David-Flyers for Art Exhibitions, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Woronov, Mary, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Yablonsky, Linda, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Group 1, Series II: Manuscripts
  - Baldwin, Ty. Homecoming., undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Bishop, John. The Devil's Music, undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Cester, Alfred. Voyage to Destruction: Letters from Morocco, undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Cooper, Dennis. Frisk (screenplay by George LaVoo), undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Cooper, Dennis. Growth., undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Cooper, Dennis and Keith Mayerson. Horror Hospital Unplugged., undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Cooper, Dennis. Period., undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Cooper, Dennis. Period., undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Cooper. Untitled Novel-in-Progress, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Chua, Lawrence. Crush., undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Chua, Lawrence. Gold by the Inch., undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Chua, Lawrence. Sweet Thing. 6/1/99, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Chua, Lawrence. Sweet Thing 7/20/00 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Dowling, Jack. Breakneck Mountain, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Draft Report to the Authors Guild Mid-List Book Study Committee., undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Estep, Maggie. Untitled Manuscript., undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Finley, Karen. Shut Up and Love Me., undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Friedman, R. Seth. Factsheet Five Magazine Reader., undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Galgut, Damon. The Quarry., undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Galgut, Damon. The Quarry., undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Gerstler, Amy. A Psychic's Childhood., undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Gillison, Samantha. The Undiscovered Country., undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Ginsberg, Allen. Death and Fire: Last Poems 1992-97., 1992-1997 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Ginsberg, Allen. Deliberate Prose: Selected Essays., undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Ginsberg, Allen. Selected Interviews., undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Gooch, Brad. ZZOMBIEOO., undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Heydt, Cassidy C. Water from the Moon., undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Hill, Lee. A Grand Guy: The Art and Life of Terry Southern., undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Jason, P. J. To Break a Nigga's Neck., undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Kertess, Klaus. First Draft of an Unfinished Novel., undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Kertess, Klaus. Scent Trip., undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Lauren, Tom. The Knitting Kit., undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Lipsyte, Sam. Venus Drive., undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Reynolds, Simon. Generation Ecstasy: Dance Music, Drugs, Technology., undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Rudnick, Paul. Isn't She Great., undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Rudnick, Paul. Isn't She Great., undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Saer, Juan JosThe Concept of Fiction., undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Savage, Jon. Teenage: The History of Youth in the Twentieth Century., undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Silverstein, Charles. Songs of My Life: Confessions of a Gay Liberationist., undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Taylor, Marvin. "A Dorian Gray Type Thing": Male-Male Desire and the Crisis of Representation in Dennis Cooper's Closer., undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Tillamn, Lynne. Bookstore: The Life and Times of Jeannette Watson and Books and Company., undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Tillman, Lynne. Nothing is Lost or Found., undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Trinidad, David. It's a Wig!, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - True Magic., undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Valdez, Nigel Jesaked (Part 1), undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Valdez, Nigel Jesaked (Part 2), undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Valdez, Nigel Jesaked (part 3), undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Wallace, Naomi. "One Flea Spare" and "Lawn Dogs" and "Icarus" by Edwin Sanchez., undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Waters, John. Pecker., undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Wojnarowicz, David. In the Shadow of the American Dream., undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Wojnarowicz, David. Postcards from America (movie adaptation), undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Wojnarowicz, David and James Romberger. Seven Miles a Second., undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Wojnarowicz, David and James Romberger. Seven Miles a Second., undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Woronov, Mary. Snake. 1/20/97, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Woronov, Mary. Snake. 3/5/97, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Woronov, Mary. Snake. 9/1/97, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Unidentified Manuscripts., undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Group 1, Series III: Affiliations
  - Academy of American Poets-Correspondence., undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Academy of American Poets., undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Association of Authors' Representatives (AAR), undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Bomb Magazine-Correspondence, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Bomb Magazine Archive, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - CLMP-Correspondnece 1996-97, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - CLMP-Correspondence. Jan.-June, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - CLMP-Correspondence. July-Dec., 1998 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - CLMP-Board. 1998 (Box 6, Folder 20)